A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial records, Political Files, Series 24 FA367
Rockefeller Archive Center
- 1961-1962, 2; 12 Cubic Feet
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - Anonymous, 1961; Folder 20 of 24 (Box 31, Folder 1067)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - Anonymous, 1961; Folder 21 of 24 (Box 31, Folder 1068)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - Anonymous, 1961; Folder 22 of 24 (Box 31, Folder 1069)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - Anonymous, 1961; Folder 23 of 24 (Box 31, Folder 1070)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - Anonymous, 1961; Folder 24 of 24 (Box 31, Folder 1071)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - Illegible, 1961; Folder 1 of 3 (Box 31, Folder 1072)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - Illegible, 1961; Folder 2 of 3 (Box 31, Folder 1073)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - Illegible, 1961; Folder 3 of 3 (Box 31, Folder 1074)
- 1963-1964, 3; 37 Cubic Feet
  This subseries contains answered and unanswered letters from 1963 and 1964. A small portion of the 1964 documents, from correspondents with names beginning with A through Bra, was destroyed prior to inclusion in the Rockefeller Family Archives due to water damage. In addition, Folders 1450 to 1460 in Box 58 (for names beginning with Sin-Sti) have evidence of past water damage and should be handled with extra care.
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (A), 1963 (Box 31, Folder 1075)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (An), 1963; Folder 1 of 2 (Box 31, Folder 1076)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (An), 1963; Folder 2 of 2 (Box 31, Folder 1077)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (B), 1963 (Box 31, Folder 1078)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Bal), 1963 (Box 32, Folder 1079)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Be), 1963 (Box 32, Folder 1080)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Ben), 1963 (Box 32, Folder 1081)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Ber), 1963 (Box 32, Folder 1082)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Bl), 1963 (Box 32, Folder 1083)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Bo), 1963 (Box 32, Folder 1084)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Br), 1963 (Box 32, Folder 1085)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Bru), 1963 (Box 32, Folder 1086)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Bu), 1963 (Box 32, Folder 1087)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (By), 1963 (Box 32, Folder 1088)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (C), 1963 (Box 33, Folder 1089)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Car), 1963 (Box 33, Folder 1090)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Ce), 1963 (Box 33, Folder 1091)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Cl), 1963 (Box 33, Folder 1092)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Co), 1963 (Box 33, Folder 1093)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Com), 1963 (Box 33, Folder 1094)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Cr), 1963 (Box 33, Folder 1095)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (D), 1963 (Box 33, Folder 1096)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Deg), 1963 (Box 33, Folder 1097)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Der), 1963 (Box 33, Folder 1098)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Dim), 1963 (Box 33, Folder 1099)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Dor), 1963 (Box 34, Folder 1100)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Du), 1963 (Box 34, Folder 1101)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (E), 1963 (Box 34, Folder 1102)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (F), 1963 (Box 34, Folder 1103)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Fi), 1963 (Box 34, Folder 1104)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Fi), 1963 (Box 34, Folder 1104A)
    Conditions Governing Access note
    Restricted material
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Fo), 1963 (Box 34, Folder 1105)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Fr), 1963 (Box 34, Folder 1106)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (G), 1963 (Box 34, Folder 1107)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Ge), 1963 (Box 34, Folder 1108)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Gi), 1963 (Box 34, Folder 1109)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Gl), 1963 (Box 35, Folder 1110)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Gon), 1963 (Box 35, Folder 1111)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Gr), 1963 (Box 35, Folder 1112)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Gu), 1963 (Box 35, Folder 1113)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (H), 1963 (Box 35, Folder 1114)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Ham), 1963 (Box 35, Folder 1115)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Has), 1963 (Box 35, Folder 1116)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Her), 1963 (Box 35, Folder 1117)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Ho), 1963 (Box 35, Folder 1118)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Hu), 1963 (Box 35, Folder 1119)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (I), 1963 (Box 35, Folder 1120)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (J), 1963 (Box 36, Folder 1121)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Ji), 1963 (Box 36, Folder 1122)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Ju), 1963 (Box 36, Folder 1123)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (K), 1963 (Box 36, Folder 1124)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Kem), 1963 (Box 36, Folder 1125)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Kn), 1963 (Box 36, Folder 1126)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Ku), 1963 (Box 36, Folder 1127)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (L), 1963 (Box 36, Folder 1128)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Le), 1963 (Box 36, Folder 1129)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Li), 1963; Folder 1 of 2 (Box 36, Folder 1130)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Li), 1963; Folder 2 of 2 (Box 36, Folder 1131)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (M), 1963 (Box 36, Folder 1132)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Mal), 1963 (Box 37, Folder 1133)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Mar), 1963 (Box 37, Folder 1134)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Mc), 1963 (Box 37, Folder 1135)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (McM), 1963 (Box 37, Folder 1136)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Me), 1963 (Box 37, Folder 1137)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Mil), 1963 (Box 37, Folder 1138)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Mo), 1963 (Box 37, Folder 1139)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Mor), 1963 (Box 37, Folder 1140)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Mu), 1963 (Box 37, Folder 1141)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (N), 1963 (Box 37, Folder 1142)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Ne), 1963 (Box 37, Folder 1143)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Ni), 1963 (Box 37, Folder 1144)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (No), 1963 (Box 37, Folder 1145)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Nu), 1963 (Box 38, Folder 1146)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (O), 1963 (Box 38, Folder 1147)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (P), 1963 (Box 38, Folder 1148)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Par), 1963 (Box 38, Folder 1149)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Pe), 1963 (Box 38, Folder 1150)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Ph), 1963 (Box 38, Folder 1151)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Pi), 1963 (Box 38, Folder 1152)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Po), 1963 (Box 38, Folder 1153)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Pr), 1963 (Box 38, Folder 1154)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Q), 1963 (Box 38, Folder 1155)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (R), 1963 (Box 38, Folder 1156)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Re), 1963 (Box 38, Folder 1157)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Rh), 1963 (Box 38, Folder 1158)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Ro), 1963 (Box 38, Folder 1159)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Ro), 1963 (Box 38, Folder 1159A)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Rol), 1963 (Box 38, Folder 1160)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Ru), 1963 (Box 39, Folder 1161)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (S), 1963 (Box 39, Folder 1162)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Sch), 1963 (Box 39, Folder 1163)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Se), 1963 (Box 39, Folder 1164)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Sh), 1963 (Box 39, Folder 1165)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (She), 1963 (Box 39, Folder 1166)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Si), 1963 (Box 39, Folder 1167)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Sk), 1963 (Box 39, Folder 1168)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Sm), 1963 (Box 39, Folder 1169)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (So), 1963 (Box 39, Folder 1170)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Sp), 1963 (Box 39, Folder 1171)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (St), 1963 (Box 39, Folder 1172)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Sti), 1963 (Box 39, Folder 1173)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Su), 1963 (Box 39, Folder 1174)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (T), 1963 (Box 40, Folder 1175)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Te), 1963 (Box 40, Folder 1176)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Th), 1963 (Box 40, Folder 1177)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Ti), 1963 (Box 40, Folder 1178)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (To), 1963 (Box 40, Folder 1179)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Tu), 1963 (Box 40, Folder 1180)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (U), 1963 (Box 40, Folder 1181)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (V), 1963 (Box 40, Folder 1182)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Ve), 1963 (Box 40, Folder 1183)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (W), 1963 (Box 40, Folder 1184)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Wan), 1963 (Box 40, Folder 1185)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (We), 1963 (Box 40, Folder 1186)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Wer), 1963 (Box 40, Folder 1187)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Wh), 1963 (Box 40, Folder 1188)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Wi), 1963 (Box 40, Folder 1189)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Wils), 1963 (Box 40, Folder 1190)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Wo), 1963 (Box 40, Folder 1191)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (X), 1963 (Box 40, Folder 1192)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Y), 1963 (Box 41, Folder 1193)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (A), 1963 (Box 41, Folder 1194)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (B), 1963 (Box 41, Folder 1195)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (C), 1963 (Box 41, Folder 1196)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (D), 1963 (Box 41, Folder 1197)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (E), 1963 (Box 41, Folder 1198)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (F), 1963 (Box 41, Folder 1199)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (G), 1963 (Box 41, Folder 1200)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (H), 1963 (Box 41, Folder 1201)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (I), 1963 (Box 41, Folder 1202)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (J), 1963 (Box 41, Folder 1203)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (K), 1963 (Box 41, Folder 1204)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (L), 1963 (Box 41, Folder 1205)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (Mc), 1963 (Box 41, Folder 1206)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (N), 1963 (Box 41, Folder 1207)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (O), 1963 (Box 41, Folder 1208)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (P), 1963 (Box 42, Folder 1209)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (R), 1963 (Box 42, Folder 1210)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (S), 1963 (Box 42, Folder 1211)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (T), 1963 (Box 42, Folder 1212)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (U-V), 1963 (Box 42, Folder 1213)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (W), 1963 (Box 42, Folder 1214)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (Y-Z), 1963 (Box 42, Folder 1215)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - Letters Regarding Goldwater Statement, 1963 (Box 42, Folder 1216)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - Letters of Support (A-B), 1963 (Box 42, Folder 1217)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - Letters of Support (C-E), 1963 (Box 42, Folder 1218)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - Letters of Support (F-H), 1963 (Box 42, Folder 1219)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - Letters of Support (I-L), 1963 (Box 42, Folder 1220)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - Letters of Support (M), 1963 (Box 42, Folder 1221)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - Letters of Support (N-Q), 1963 (Box 43, Folder 1222)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - Letters of Support (R), 1963 (Box 43, Folder 1223)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - Letters of Support (S-Sh), 1963 (Box 43, Folder 1224)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - Letters of Support (Si-Sy), 1963 (Box 43, Folder 1225)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - Letters of Support (T-V), 1963 (Box 43, Folder 1226)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - Letters of Support (W), 1963 (Box 43, Folder 1227)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - Letters of Support (Y-Z), 1963 (Box 43, Folder 1228)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Bre), 1964 (Box 43, Folder 1229)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Bro), 1964 (Box 43, Folder 1230)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Brow), 1964 (Box 43, Folder 1231)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Bru), 1964 (Box 43, Folder 1232)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Bu), 1964 (Box 43, Folder 1233)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Bur), 1964; Folder 1 of 2 (Box 44, Folder 1234)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Bur), 1964; Folder 2 of 2 (Box 44, Folder 1235)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (But), 1964 (Box 44, Folder 1236)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (C), 1964 (Box 44, Folder 1237)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Cal), 1964 (Box 44, Folder 1238)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Cam), 1964 (Box 44, Folder 1239)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Car), 1964; Folder 1 of 2 (Box 44, Folder 1240)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Car), 1964; Folder 2 of 2 (Box 44, Folder 1241)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Cat), 1964 (Box 44, Folder 1242)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Ce), 1964 (Box 44, Folder 1243)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Ch), 1964 (Box 44, Folder 1244)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Che), 1964 (Box 44, Folder 1245)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Cho), 1964 (Box 44, Folder 1246)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Ci), 1964 (Box 44, Folder 1247)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Cl), 1964 (Box 44, Folder 1248)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Co), 1964 (Box 44, Folder 1249)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Cok), 1964 (Box 45, Folder 1250)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Com), 1964; Folder 1 of 2 (Box 45, Folder 1251)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Com), 1964; Folder 2 of 2 (Box 45, Folder 1252)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Cos), 1964 (Box 45, Folder 1253)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Cr), 1964 (Box 45, Folder 1254)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Cri), 1964 (Box 45, Folder 1255)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Cu), 1964 (Box 45, Folder 1256)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (D), 1964 (Box 45, Folder 1257)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Dar), 1964 (Box 45, Folder 1258)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Dav), 1964 (Box 45, Folder 1259)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (De), 1964 (Box 45, Folder 1260)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Dem), 1964 (Box 45, Folder 1261)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Det), 1964 (Box 45, Folder 1262)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Di), 1964 (Box 45, Folder 1263)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Dik), 1964 (Box 46, Folder 1264)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Din), 1964 (Box 46, Folder 1265)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Do), 1964 (Box 46, Folder 1266)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Dok), 1964 (Box 46, Folder 1267)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Dom), 1964 (Box 46, Folder 1268)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Dos), 1964 (Box 46, Folder 1269)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Dr), 1964 (Box 46, Folder 1270)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Du), 1964 (Box 46, Folder 1271)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Dum), 1964 (Box 46, Folder 1272)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Dut), 1964 (Box 46, Folder 1273)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (E), 1964 (Box 46, Folder 1274)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (El), 1964 (Box 46, Folder 1275)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Em), 1964 (Box 46, Folder 1276)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Er), 1964 (Box 46, Folder 1277)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Ev), 1964 (Box 46, Folder 1278)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (F), 1964 (Box 46, Folder 1279)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Fam), 1964 (Box 46, Folder 1280)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Fas), 1964 (Box 46, Folder 1281)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Fe), 1964 (Box 47, Folder 1282)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Fek), 1964 (Box 47, Folder 1283)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Fem), 1964 (Box 47, Folder 1284)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Fer), 1964 (Box 47, Folder 1285)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Fi), 1964 (Box 47, Folder 1286)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Fim), 1964 (Box 47, Folder 1287)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Fo), 1964 (Box 47, Folder 1288)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Fok), 1964 (Box 47, Folder 1289)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Fr), 1964 (Box 47, Folder 1290)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Fre), 1964 (Box 47, Folder 1291)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Fri), 1964 (Box 47, Folder 1292)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Fu), 1964 (Box 47, Folder 1293)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (G), 1964 (Box 47, Folder 1294)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Gar), 1964 (Box 47, Folder 1295)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Ge), 1964 (Box 47, Folder 1296)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Gi), 1964 (Box 47, Folder 1297)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Gl), 1964 (Box 48, Folder 1298)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Go), 1964 (Box 48, Folder 1299)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Gok), 1964 (Box 48, Folder 1300)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Gom), 1964 (Box 48, Folder 1301)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Got), 1964 (Box 48, Folder 1302)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Gr), 1964 (Box 48, Folder 1303)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Gre), 1964 (Box 48, Folder 1304)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Gri), 1964 (Box 48, Folder 1305)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Gro), 1964 (Box 48, Folder 1306)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Gu), 1964 (Box 48, Folder 1307)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (H), 1964 (Box 48, Folder 1308)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Hal), 1964 (Box 48, Folder 1309)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Ham), 1964 (Box 48, Folder 1310)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Har), 1964; Folder 1 of 2 (Box 48, Folder 1311)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Har), 1964; Folder 2 of 2 (Box 48, Folder 1312)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Hat), 1964 (Box 48, Folder 1313)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (He), 1964 (Box 49, Folder 1314)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Hek), 1964 (Box 49, Folder 1315)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Hem), 1964 (Box 49, Folder 1316)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Hes), 1964 (Box 49, Folder 1317)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Hi), 1964 (Box 49, Folder 1318)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Him), 1964 (Box 49, Folder 1319)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Ho), 1964 (Box 49, Folder 1320)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Hol), 1964 (Box 49, Folder 1321)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Hom), 1964 (Box 49, Folder 1322)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Hor), 1964 (Box 49, Folder 1323)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Hu), 1964; Folder 1 of 2 (Box 49, Folder 1324)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Hu), 1964; Folder 2 of 2 (Box 49, Folder 1325)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (I), 1964 (Box 49, Folder 1326)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (J), 1964 (Box 49, Folder 1327)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Jak), 1964 (Box 50, Folder 1328)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Je), 1964 (Box 50, Folder 1329)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Jo), 1964 (Box 50, Folder 1330)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Jon), 1964 (Box 50, Folder 1331)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Ju), 1964 (Box 50, Folder 1332)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (K), 1964 (Box 50, Folder 1333)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Kar), 1964 (Box 50, Folder 1334)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Ke), 1964 (Box 50, Folder 1335)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Kem), 1964 (Box 50, Folder 1336)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Ki), 1964 (Box 50, Folder 1337)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Kn), 1964 (Box 50, Folder 1338)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Ko), 1964 (Box 50, Folder 1339)